Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
- Writing and Research Materials, 1950 - 2006; Series V
  - Syndicated articles
    - "Tell It Straight to North Korea—But Talking May Not Be Enough," International Herald Tribune, Jul 4, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - "Expect Favorites in Semifinals," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 9, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - "Final Four a Blend of Familiar, Unknown," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 16, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 21)
    - "Unfair Rule Puts an End to Fair Final," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 18, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 22)
    - "It's an Alliance, Not a Relic," Washington Post, Aug 16, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 23)
    - "A Good Idea—Whose Time Is Not Yet Come," New York Post, Sep 13, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 24)
    - "Out of Haiti—Fast," Washington Post, Sep 25, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 25)
    - "Beginning of the End of the Kohl Era," Washington Post, Oct 25, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 26)
    - "Expand NATO Now," Washington Post, Dec 19, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 27)
    - "The Case for U.S. Loan Guarantees to Mexico," New York Post, Jan 31, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 28)
    - "Building a Consensus on U.S. Foreign Policy," New York Post, Mar 7, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 29)
    - "Challenge to America: Political, Not Economic," New York Post, Apr 25, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 30)
    - "For U.S. Leadership, a Moment Missed," Washington Post, May 12, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 31)
    - "Toward a Moment of Truth in Bosnia," Washington Post, Jun 11, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 32)
    - "Four Proposals to Get the United States and China off Their Collision Course," International Herald Tribune, Jul 24, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 33)
    - "Bosnia: Only Just Beginning...," Washington Post, Sep 11, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 34)
    - "What Is the Mission?," Washington Post, Oct 22, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 35)
    - "My Fallen Friend," Washington Post, Nov 12, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 36)
    - "Bosnia: Reasons for Care," Washington Post, Dec 10, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 37)
    - "Stone's Nixon," Washington Post, Jan 24, 1996 (Box 216, Folder 38)
    - "The Stakes with China," Washington Post, Mar 31, 1996 (Box 216, Folder 39)
    - "Moscow and Beijing: A Declaration of Independence," Washington Post, May 14, 1996 (Box 216, Folder 40)
    - "Retooling the Process for Peace," Washington Post, Jul 1, 1996 (Box 216, Folder 41)
    - "America in the Eye of a Hurricane," Washington Post, Sep 8, 1996 (Box 216, Folder 42)
    - "No Objective, No Will," Washington Post, Oct 6, 1996 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - "The Bottom Line of the Mideast Peace Process," New York Post, Nov 19, 1996 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - "NATO: Make It Stronger, Make It Larger," Washington Post, Jan 14, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - "Helsinki: Fiasco," Washington Post, Mar 30, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - "Fulfilling the Historic Promise of the Americas," New York Post, Apr 29, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - "The Dilution of NATO," Washington Post, Jun 8, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - "Let's Cooperate with China," Washington Post, Jul 6, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - "The Oslo Piecemeal Process," Washington Post, Aug 24, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - "Limits to What the U.S. Can Do in Bosnia," Washington Post, Sep 22, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - "The Oil Deal with Iran," Washington Post, Oct 28, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - "No Carrots for Saddam," Washington Post, Dec 7, 1997 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - "The Asian Collapse: One Fix Does Not Fit All Economics," Washington Post, Feb 9, 1998 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - "Our Shilly-Shally 'Strategy' on Saddam," Washington Post, Mar 23, 1998 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - "A Name Union in Europe," Washington Post, May 12, 1998 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - "India and Pakistan: After the Explosions," Washington Post, Jun 8, 1998 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - "Perils of Globalism," Washington Post, Oct 5, 1998 (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - "Bring Saddam Down," Washington Post, Nov 29, 1998 (Box 217, Folder 17)
    - "Move on to Peace," Washington Post, Feb 2, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 18)
    - "No U.S. Ground Forces for Kosovo," Washington Post, Feb 22, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 19)
    - "Single-Issue Diplomacy Won't Work," Washington Post, Apr 27, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 20)
    - "U.S. Mediation Essential," Washington Post, Jul 19, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 21)
    - "The End of NATO as We Know It?," Washington Post, Aug 15, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 22)
    - "Storm Clouds Gathering," Washington Post, Sep 7, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 23)
    - "Test-Ban Treaty: Let's Wait Awhile," by John Deutch, Brent Scowcroft and Kissinger, Washington Post, Oct 6, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 24)
    - "Playing Politics with the Test Ban Treaty," Washington Post, Nov 23, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 25)
    - "Making a Go of Globalization," Washington Post, Dec 20, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 26)
    - "Our Nearsighted World Vision," Washington Post, Jan 10, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 27)
    - "The Next President's First Obligation," Washington Post, Feb 9, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 28)
    - "Mission to Moscow," Washington Post, May 15, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 29)
    - "In the Middle East, Clashing Concepts of Peace," Washington Post, Jun 26, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 30)
    - "The Case for a Piece-by-Piece Peace," Washington Post, Aug 28, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 31)
    - "Best for Mexico's Fox If We Mute U.S. Triumphalism," Houston Chronicle, Oct 1, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 32)
    - "The Peace Paradox," Washington Post, Dec 4, 2000 (Box 217, Folder 33)
    - "An Alliance That Sees Eye to Eye," Washington Post, Jan 24, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 34)
    - "A Road through Seoul," Washington Post, Mar 6, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - "Brazil's 'Destiny': An Obstacle to Free Trade?," Washington Post, May 15, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - "Giving Europe's Leaders Something to Think About," Washington Post, Jul 5, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - "What to Do with the New Russia," Washington Post, Aug 14, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - "Destroy the Network," Washington Post, Sep 12, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - "Moderation Is No Virtue Against Terrorism," Los Angeles Times, Sep 14, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - "Where Do We Go from Here?," Washington Post, Nov 6, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - "At Home in Babe Ruth's House," New York Post, Nov 15, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - "A New World Dawn," New York Post, Dec 2, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - "Phase II and Iraq," Washington Post, Jan 13, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - "Answering the 'Axis' Critics," Washington Post, Mar 5, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - "Mideast Peace—in Stages," Washington Post, May 14, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - "The Stakes in Kashmir," Washington Post, Jun 6, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - "The New World (Cup) Order," New York Post, Jul 7, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - "Our Intervention in Iraq," Washington Post, Aug 12, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - "Consult and Control: Bywords for Battling the New Enemy," Washington Post, Sep 16, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - "The 'Made in Berlin' Generation," Washington Post, Oct 30, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - "A Dangerous Divergence," Washington Post, Dec 10, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 18)
    - "International Community Should Not Bow to North Korea's Nuclear Blackmail," Jan 12, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 19)
    - "Role Reversal and Alliance Realities," Washington Post, Feb 10, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 20)
    - "The U.S. Can't Go It Alone on N. Korea," Washington Post, Mar 17, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 21)
    - "Repairing the Atlantic Alliance," Washington Post, Apr 14, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 22)
    - "Road Map Realities," New York Post, Jun 22, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 23)
    - "The Six-Power Route to Resolution," Washington Post, Aug 18, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 24)
    - "Needed: A Sense of Common Purpose," Washington Post, Nov 2, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 25)
    - "In Israel's Fence, an Opening to Accord," Washington Post, Dec 22, 2003 (Box 218, Folder 26)
    - "A Date of Destiny for Iraq," Washington Post, Feb 11, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 27)
    - "Intervention with a Vision," Washington Post, Apr 11, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 28)
    - "Discarding Blinders in the Mideast," Washington Post, May 9, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 29)
    - "A Global Order in Flux," Washington Post, Jul 9, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 30)
    - "Better Intelligence Reform," Washington Post, Aug 16, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 31)
    - "A New Opening for Mideast Peace," Washington Post, Dec 3, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 32)
    - "Results, Not Timetables, Matter in Iraq," by George Shultz and Kissinger, Washington Post, Jan 25, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 33)
    - "Iran: A Nuclear Test Case," Washington Post, Mar 8, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 34)
    - "Implementing Bush's Vision," Washington Post, May 16, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 35)
    - "China: Containment Won't Work," Washington Post, Jun 13, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 36)
    - "Lessons for an Exit Strategy," Washington Post, Aug 12, 2005 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - "Will Germany's Coalition Work?," Washington Post, Nov 22, 2005 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - "How to Exit Iraq," Washington Post, Dec 18, 2005 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - "What's Needed from Hamas," Washington Post, Feb 27, 2006 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - "Working with India," Washington Post, Mar 20, 2006 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - "The Rules on Preventative Force," Washington Post, Apr 9, 2006 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - "A Nuclear Test for Diplomacy," Washington Post, May 16, 2006 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - "The Next Steps with Iran," Washington Post, Jul 31, 2006 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - "After Lebanon," Washington Post, Sep 13, 2006 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate thesis
    - "The Meaning of History"-copy of final submitted version [1 of 3], 1950 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - "The Meaning of History"-copy of final submitted version [2 of 3], 1950 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - "The Meaning of History"-copy of final submitted version [3 of 3], 1950 (Box 219, Folder 12)
- Cartoons, Circa 1969-1989; Series VI
  The cartoons are a collection of political cartoons and caricatures of Kissinger, primarily concerning his time in government from 1969 to 1977 and his emergence as an international celebrity. There is only one 1989 cartoon from later years. Many of the cartoons are ink drawings while others are prints. Frequently, the cartoons are signed by the artist and include a short note to Kissinger. Most of the cartoons appeared in American newspapers and magazines, but a few of the cartoons come from publications abroad. A larger collection of similar cartoons can be found in Part II of the Henry A. Kissinger papers.
  Series VI is arranged into two subseries: General and Oversized.
  - General
    - Cartoons, 1971 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Cartoons, 1972 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Cartoons, 1972 January 28 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Cartoons, 1972 February 3 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Cartoons [1 of 3], Undated, circa 1969-circa 1976 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Cartoons [2 of 3], Undated, circa 1969-circa 1976 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Cartoons [3 of 3], Undated, circa 1969-circa 1976 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Oversized
    - Cartoons, 1972 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Cartoons, 1972 February 13 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Cartoons, 1972 February 13-May 14 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Cartoons, 1975 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Cartoons, 1975 August 11 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Cartoons [includes correspondence], 1976 January 20-August 11 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Cartoons, 1976 September 5 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - Cartoons, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - Cartoons [1 of 2], Undated, circa 1969-circa 1976 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Cartoons [2 of 2], Undated, circa 1969-circa 1976 (Box 221, Folder 10)
- Photographs, 1938 - 2009; Series VII
  The photographs document Kissinger’s life from the 1930s to 2009, but only a small number concern the years prior to 1969 and only one dates from after 2006. Photographs from 1977 to 2001 are limited, and a much larger collection of photographs from this period can be found in Part II of the Henry A. Kissinger papers. The files in this series from 2002 to 2006 supplement the photograph files found in Part II that run to 2001. They depict Kissinger’s professional and personal life during this period while he remained a prominent author and public commentator on international affairs and the principle at the international consulting firm Kissinger Associates.
  The files from his government service years cover selected events, often Kissinger’s trips abroad. In general, official White House photographs and photographs from the American press are not included in these files, which are primarily composed of photographs taken by private individuals, professional photographers, and foreign press or governments. A number of folders contain correspondence, usually a single letter that accompanied the photographs. The Rodman files appear to be photographs that Kissinger’s close personal aide Peter W. Rodman took, usually while traveling with Kissinger when he was secretary of state. Likewise, most of the photograph albums commemorate Kissinger’s service as secretary of state.
  Series VII is arranged into three subseries: General, Rodman (Peter W.) files, and Albums.
  - General
    - Kissinger with brother in Germany, Circa 1930s (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Kissinger family, 1938 August 28 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Kissinger in Army, Eijgelshaven, Netherlands, 1944 November (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Israel [?], Circa 1960s (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Kissinger portrait, Circa 1960s (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Kissinger portrait, 1967 May (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Japan [?], Circa 1968 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Broome Technical Community College, 1968 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Fort Benning, 1968 February 13 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Nixon, Richard with Henry, Louis, and Paula Kissinger at the White House, Circa 1969 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, Richard with Kissinger, Circa 1969-circa 1974 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Kissinger with National Security Council (NSC) staff, 1969 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified individuals and David Kissinger with Kissinger, Circa 1970s (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Kissinger portraits, Circa 1970s-circa 1990s (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Kissinger with unidentified individuals, 1970s-2000s (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Kissinger with family, 1971, undated (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Kissinger getting into a car, 1971 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Gandhi, Indira and Kenneth B. Keating with Kissinger in India, 1971 July (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Zedong, Mao with Kissinger in Beijing, 1971 October 21 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Japan, Circa 1972 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Le Duc Tho and Xuan Thuy with Kissinger, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 19)
    - Nobel Prize dinner and Nobel laureates, Circa 1973 (Box 222, Folder 20)
    - Katzir, Ephraim, Circa 1973-circa 1975 (Box 222, Folder 21)
    - Mao, Zedong and Zhou Enlai with Kissinger, 1973 February (Box 222, Folder 22)
    - Zhou, Enlai with Kissinger in Great Hall of the People, 1973 November 10 (Box 222, Folder 23)
    - Japan, Nov 21, 1974 [includes correspondence], 1974 - 1975 (Box 222, Folder 24)
    - Photographs selected for possible use in Years of Renewal [1 of 5], 1974 - 1976 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Photographs selected for possible use in Years of Renewal [2 of 5], 1974 - 1976 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Photographs selected for possible use in Years of Renewal [3 of 5], 1974 - 1976 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Photographs selected for possible use in Years of Renewal [4 of 5], 1974 - 1976 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Photographs selected for possible use in Years of Renewal [5 of 5], 1974 - 1976 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Morita, Akio with Kissinger-photocopies, 1974 - 1993 (Box 222, Folder 25)
    - Completion of Egyptian-Israeli Disengagement Accord at prime minister's residence, 1974 January 18 (Box 222, Folder 26)
    - Middle East, 1974 February 25-March 4 (Box 222, Folder 27)
    - Brezhnev, Leonid with Kissinger in Moscow, 1974 March (Box 222, Folder 28)
    - Boumédiene, Houari meeting with Kissinger in Algiers, 1974 April 29-30 (Box 222, Folder 29)
    - Giscard d'Estaing, Jacques with Kissinger, 1974 June or July (Box 222, Folder 30)
    - Ford, Gerald R. with Kissinger in the Oval Office, 1974 August 23 (Box 222, Folder 31)
    - World Food Conference, Rome, 1974 November (Box 222, Folder 32)
    - China, 1974 November 25-28 (Box 222, Folder 33)
    - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, 1975 February 15 (Box 222, Folder 34)
    - Schmidt, Helmut and Hans Dietrich Genscher with Kissinger in Bonn, 1975 February 16 (Box 222, Folder 35)
    - Gromyko, Andrei with Kissinger in Vienna, 1975 May 18-20 (Box 222, Folder 36)
    - Ford, Gerald R. with Kissinger in Bonn [includes correspondence], 1975 July 26-28 (Box 222, Folder 37)
    - Ford, Gerald R. with Kissinger at Conference on Security and Co-operation in Europe (CSCE), Helsinki, 1975 July 31-August 1 (Box 222, Folder 38)
    - Amman, Jordan, 1975 August (Box 222, Folder 39)
    - Ford, Gerald R. with Kissinger in Belgrade, 1975 August 3-4 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Sinai II Agreement negotiations, 1975 August 20-September 3 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Sinai II Agreement, 1975 August 20-September 4 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - China, 1975 December (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Lima [includes correspondence] [1 of 2], 1976 February 18-19 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Lima [2 of 2], 1976 February 18-19 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Rio de Janeiro, 1976 February 19-22 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Facio, Gonzalo J. with Kissinger, 1976 February 23 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Liberia, 1976 May (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - NATO ministerial meeting, Oslo, 1976 May (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Kissinger, Nancy in Chile, 1976 June (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Santo Domingo, 1976 June 6 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Mexico [includes correspondence], 1976 June 10 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Echeverría, Luis with Henry and Nancy Kissinger in Mexico, 1976 June 11 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Yucatan, 1976 June 12 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Organization of Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) meeting, Paris, 1976 June 21-22 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - Tehran [includes correspondence], 1976 August 6-8 (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - Lahore, Pakistan, 1976 August 9 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Saud al-Faisal, Prince of Saudi Arabia, with Kissinger in Washington, DC, 1976 October (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Inauguration of Jose Lopez Portillo, Mexico, 1976 November 29-Dec3 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - London, 1976 December 11-12 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Ford, Gerald R. with Kissinger at Pan American Union, 1977 January 14 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Thatcher, Margaret with Kissinger, 1979 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Reagan, Nancy and Ronald with Kissinger [includes correspondence], Circa 1980s (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Italian soccer team, Alassio, 1982 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird with David, Henry, and Nancy Kissinger [includes correspondence], 1984 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - Hayashi, Yoshiro with Kissinger-photocopy, 1985 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - Reagan, Nancy and Ronald with Henry and Nancy Kissinger at the White House, 1985 June 12 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Kissinger at North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) meeting-photocopy [includes correspondence], 1987 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1988 June 9 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Jiang, Zemin with Kissinger in China, Circa 1990s (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Lacalle Herrera, Luis Alberto, Circa 1990 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - Maccioni, Sirio and others with Henry and Nancy Kissinger in Italy, 1990 (Box 224, Folder 16)
    - Clinton, Bill with Kissinger, 1995 March 1 (Box 224, Folder 17)
    - Clinton, Bill, Al Gore, and others with Kissinger in the Oval Office, 1995 July 13 (Box 224, Folder 18)
    - Clinton, Bill meeting with Kissinger at the White House, 1995 July 13 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - Baker Institute Conference, 1997 (Box 224, Folder 20)
    - Kissinger portrait, Circa 1998-circa 1999 (Box 224, Folder 21)
    - Clinton, Bill shaking hands with Henry and Nancy Kissinger, 1998 September 16 (Box 224, Folder 22)
    - Clinton, Bill with Kissinger at the White House, 1999 July 18 (Box 224, Folder 23)
    - Ford, Gerald R. and family with Bill and Hillary Clinton and Kissinger, 1999 August 11 (Box 224, Folder 24)
    - Distinguished Americans Supporting China Permanent Normal Trade Relations event at the White House, 2000 May 9 (Box 224, Folder 25)
    - Mandela, Nelson with Kissinger at Forstmann Little Conference, Aspen, Circa 2001 (Box 224, Folder 26)
    - John Paul II with Henry and Nancy Kissinger at the Vatican, 2001 (Box 224, Folder 27)
    - Kissinger portraits by Arthur Elgort [includes correspondence], 2001 (Box 224, Folder 28)
    - Kissinger at Peking University, 2001 March 21 (Box 224, Folder 29)
    - Agnelli, Gianni, Antonio Martino, and Kissinger, 2001 May (Box 224, Folder 30)
    - Bloomberg, Michael and Ariel Sharon at reception at Israeli Consulate, 2001 June 25 (Box 224, Folder 31)
    - Elkann, Lapo and Kissinger at Teach for America classroom visit, 2001 October 17 (Box 224, Folder 32)
    - Blackwill, Robert D. with Kissinger in India, 2002 January (Box 224, Folder 33)
    - Visit to 22nd Special Air Service Regiment, London, 2002 January 11 (Box 224, Folder 34)
    - Vance, Grace with Kissinger, 2002 January 19 (Box 224, Folder 35)
    - Kissinger reading in Dick Cheney's office, 2002 January 25 (Box 224, Folder 36)
    - 113th International Olympic Committee session, 2002 February 4-6 (Box 224, Folder 37)
    - Cohen, William with Kissinger at Woodrow Wilson Award for Public Service reception, 2002 March 7 (Box 224, Folder 38)
    - Gorbachev, Mikhail, Mercedes and Sid Bass, and Kissinger, 2002 March 12 (Box 224, Folder 39)
    - Baseball Hall of Fame dinner, 2002 March 13 (Box 224, Folder 40)
    - Karimov, Islam with Kissinger at Be'er Hagolah Institutes reception, 2002 March 13 (Box 224, Folder 41)
    - Genscher, Hans Dietrich with Kissinger in Germany [includes correspondence], 2002 March 16 (Box 224, Folder 42)
    - Kissinger speaking at Southern Methodist University, Dallas [includes correspondence], 2002 March 27 (Box 224, Folder 43)
    - Hutchinson, Kay Bailey, John Mendelsohn, and Kissinger at Anderson Cancer Center, Houston [includes correspondence], 2002 March 28 (Box 224, Folder 44)
    - Members of Chinese and United States delegation with Henry and Nancy Kissinger, 2002 April (Box 224, Folder 45)
    - Dan David Prize awards ceremony, Tel Aviv University, 2002 May (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Jintao, Hu with Kissinger at National Committee on United States-China Relations (NCUSCR)/America-China Forum (ACF) dinner, Washington, DC, 2002 May 2 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Kissinger speaking at the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) in Washington, DC [includes correspondence], 2002 May 7 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Brazilian-American Chamber of Commerce dinner, 2002 May 16 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Iwatani, Don with Kissinger, 2002 May 16 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - American Council on Germany McCloy Awards Dinner [includes correspondence], 2002 June (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Barre, Raymond and Eva with Henry and Nancy Kissinger, 2002 June 6 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Visit to Smart factory in Hambach, France, with Bosch Advisory Committee, 2002 June 7 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Xaverian High School Joe DiMaggio Award dinner, 2002 June 9 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Félix Houphouët-Boigny Peace Prize ceremony [includes correspondence], 2002 June 21 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Shultz, George and Stephen Davison Bechtel with Kissinger at Bohemian Grove [includes correspondence], 2002 July 18-21 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Appeal of Conscience dinner [includes correspondence], 2002 October 1 (Box 225, Folder 12)